Finding Aid for the Stanley Chase Papers LSC.1090
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Theater, 1946-1989.; 34 boxes, 5 oversize boxes, 4 map folders.
  - Subseries 1D: Miscellaneous, 1953-1989.; 3.5 boxes.
    - Waiting for Godot--Correspondence., 1955. (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Correspondence related to the production of Waiting for Godot. Includes a signed, typewritten letter to Chase from Samuel Beckett regarding American production rights.
    - Miscellaneous photographs and negatives., ca. 1950s. (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives of unidentified people.
    - Job applications., 1958. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Fire to the Sea--Miscellaneous., 1958-1959. (Box 27, Folder 5)
      Correspondence, budgets and notes related to the attempted production of Gore Vidal's play, Fire to the Sea.
    - Fire to the Sea--Preliminary expenses., 1958. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Fire to the Sea--Clippings., 1958. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Saroyan, William--Clippings., 1957-1958. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Capalbo, Carmen--Clippings., 1957-1958. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Production investments and projects in development., 1955-1960. (Box 27, Folder 10)
      Correspondence and documentation related to projects in development and investments in other productions.
    - Happy End., 1972. (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Script. Melodrama with songs. Lyrics by Bertolt Brecht, music by Kurt Weill, original German play by Dorothy Lane, American adaptation and lyrics by Michael Feingold.
    - Carlton, Bob. Return to the Forbidden Planet., 1989. (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Script.
    - Casablanca., no date. (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Script. A musical based on the motion picture and the book by Julius Epstein. Stanley Chase Productions.
    - "An Untitled Musical Based on the Motion Picture Casablanca.", no date. (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Script. Music bu Author Schwartz, lyrics by Leo Robin. Based on the book by Julius Epstein.
    - Hart, Moss and Cole Porter. Jubilee!., 1973. (Box 28, Folder 5)
      Script. Includes a letter from Florence Leeds of the Cole Porter Musical and Literary Property Trust.
    - Elstein, Julius J. Class., no date. (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Script. International Creative Management.
    - Brecht, Bertolt and Kurt Weill. Mahagonny Songplay., 1971. (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Script. Authorized translation by Michael Feingold. Copyright by Stefan S. Brecht.
    - Coxe, Daniel M. and Alexander Dubin. An Amazing Woman: A Play in Three Acts., 1974 October 25. (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Script for a musical play. Stanley Chase Productions.
    - Leokum, Arkady. Friends and Enemies., no date. (Box 28, Folder 9)
      Script. Mel Bloom and Associates.
    - Hailey, Oliver. Who's Happy Now?, no date. (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Script. Comedy in three acts. Lyrics by Dion McGregor, music by Michael Barr.
    - Minoff, Lee. Romp., 1968. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Ferguson, Clifford Wesley. The Saga of Big Boy., no date. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Lyndon, Barre. The Big Tickle., no date. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Gethers, Steven. Cracker Money., no date. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Kopit, Arthur. Indians., 1968. (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Script. A play in two acts.
    - Vidal, Gore. Fire to the Sea., no date. (Box 29, Folder 7)
      Script. A play in three acts.
    - Anouilh, Jean. Ornifle., no date. (Box 29, Folder 8)
      Script. Translated by Lucienne Hill.
  - Subseries 1E: Playbills and programs, ca. 1950-1960.; 5 boxes.
    Assorted playbills and programs; playbills are arranged by theater.
    - Alvin Theatre. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Ambassador Theatre. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - American Shakespeare Festival. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - ANTA Theatre. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Belasco Theatre. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Bijou Theatre. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Biltmore Theatre. (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Booth Theatre. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Broadhurst Theatre. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Broadway Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Brooks Atkinson Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Carmen Jones Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Circle in the Square Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Cornet Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Cort Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Douglas Fairbanks Theater. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Empire Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Ethel Barrymore Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Eugene O'Neill Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Forty-Sixth Street Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Fulton Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Gershwin Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Helen Hayes Theatre. (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Henry Miller's Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Hudson Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Imperial Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - John Golden Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Lincoln Center. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Little Hippodrone. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Longacre Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Lunt-Fontanne Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Lyceum Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Majestic Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Mark Hellinger Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Martin Beck Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Metropolitan Opera House. (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Minetta Lane Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Morosco Theatre. (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Music Box. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - National Theatre. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - New York City Center of Music and Drama. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Phoenix Theatre. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Playhouse. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Plymouth Theatre. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Royale Theatre. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - St. James Theatre. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Shubert Theatre. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Vanderbilt Theatre. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Theatre. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Winter Garden. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Ziegfeld Theatre. (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous programs. (Box 34)
- Series 2: Film, 1955-2001.; 38 boxes, 4 oversize boxes, 18 map folders.
  This series consists of production files and business files, original production design drawings, posters, publicity materials, press clippings, ephemera, and various scripts. Arranged in subseries A-F as follows:
  The Hell With Heroes, 1967-1968.
  Colossus: The Forbin Project, 1965-1970.
  High Ballin', 1976-1986.
  Mack the Knife, 1955-1990.
  Miscellaneous productions, ca. 1973-1981.
  Scripts, 1956-2001.
  - Subseries 2A: The Hell With Heroes, 1967-1968.; 1.5 boxes, 1.5 oversize box, 5 map folders.
    This subseries consists of production files, original production design drawings, posters, photographs, publicity materials, and scripts. The Hell With Heroes was released in the United States on August 28, 1968 under Universal Pictures, and produced by Stanley Chase. The film starred Rod Taylor and Claudia Cardinale, and was directed by Joseph Sargent. Screenplay by Harold Livingston and Halsted Welles.
    - Miscellaneous (folder 1 of 2)., 1967. (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Cast and crew lists, set memoranda, snapshots, and shooting schedules.
    - Miscellaneous (folder 2 of 2)., 1967. (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Inter-office communications, interview schedules, party invitation lists, and script corrections.
    - Call sheets., 1967. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Production cost reports., 1967. (Box 49, Folder 4-6)
    - Publicity., 1967. (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Articles and photographs.
    - Stock shot and credits material., 1967. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Score., no date. (Box 49, Folder 9)
      Musical score and notes.
    - Second draft screenplay., 1967. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Revised final screenplay., 1967. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Notes and memoranda., 1967. (Box 49, Folder 12)
      Assorted handwritten and typewritten notes about the productions, including screenplay edits, memoranda and cast lists.
    - Correspondence., 1967. (Box 50, Folder 1)
      Assorted studio and Motion Picture Association of American memoranda and correspondence. Contract memos.
    - Photographs., 1967. (Box 50, Folder 2-3)
      Black and white photographs of cast, crew and set. See box 66 for oversized photos of Chase with cast and crew. Includes stills from production.
    - Production budget., 1967 July. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Promotional brochures., ca. 1967. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Production design drawings by G. Meyer. Desert encampments., ca. 1967. (Box 50, Folder 6)
      Acrylic on board; each piece measures approx. 10" x 6." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawing by G. Meyer. North African Air Freight (ground view)., ca. 1967. (Box 64, Folder 1)
      Acrylic on board; measures approx. 12" x 36." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawing by G. Meyer. North African Air Freight (birds eye view)., ca. 1967. (Box 64, Folder 2)
      Acrylic on board; measures approx. 18" x 27." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawing by John Solie. Beach encampment., ca. 1967. (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Production design storyboard by G. Meyer. Jeep escape., ca. 1967. (Box 64, Folder 4)
      Acrylic; 5 3" x 8" panels, mounted on board. Unsigned.
    - Production design drawing by John Solie. Airport and jets., ca. 1967. (Box 64, Folder 5)
      Graphite and watercolor on tracing paper; approx. 9" x 22." Signed by the artist.
    - Italian publicity posters., 1968.; [2 boxes]. (Box 68, Box 69)
    - American publicity posters., 1968. (Box 70)
    - Costume designs for Claudia Cardinale., ca. 1967. (Box 87, Folder 1)
      14 original wardrobe fashion sketches for Cardinale, some with fabric swatches. The costume designer for the production was Jean Louis; the drawings are unsigned.
    - Production design drawing by G. Meyer. Nighttime city harbor scene., ca. 1967. (Box 96)
      Acrylic on board; approx. 40" x 20." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawing by G. Meyer. Restaurant scene., ca. 1967. (Box 97)
  - Subseries 2B: Colossus: The Forbin Project, 1965-1970.; 5.5 boxes, 2.25 oversized boxes, 12 map folders.
    This subseries consists of production files, original production design drawings, posters, photographs, publicity materials, and scripts. Colossus: The Forbin Project was widely released in the United States on April 8, 1970 under Universal Pictures, and produced by Stanley Chase. The film starred Eric Braeden and Susan Clark, and was directed by Joseph Sargent. The screenplay was adapted by James Bridges from the D.F Jones novel Colossus.
    - Colossus logo design., no date. (Box 50, Folder 7)
      Preliminary design of a sample Colossus logo.
    - Publicity., no date. (Box 50, Folder 8)
      Small format posters.
    - Step outlines., 1967 April 21. (Box 50, Folder 9)
      Original outlines; include notes from meetings.
    - Screenplay--First draft manuscript., no date. (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Author's typed manuscript, and unrevised draft with notes.
    - Screenplay--Revised final., 1967 June 16. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Screenplay--First draft., 1967 July 20. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Screenplay--Revised first draft., 1967 August 8. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Screenplay--Second draft., 1967 September 11. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay--Revised second draft (folder 1 of 2)., 1967 October 23. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Screenplay--Revised second draft (folder 2 of 2)., 1967 December 2. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Screenplay--Third draft., 1967 December 13. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Screenplay--Revised third draft., 1968 January 30. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Screenplay--Final., 1968 September 24. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Screenplay--Revised final with production notes., 1968 October 9. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay--Second revised final., 1968 October 31. (Box 52, Folder 6)
      Annotated.
    - Photographic materials., 1968-1970. (Box 53, Folder 1-5)
      Five folders of prints and negatives from production, stills, and photographs of production design drawings.
    - Photographic materials., ca. 1970. (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
    - Publicity., ca. 1970. (Box 54, Folder 3)
      Original clippings and magazine articles about Colossus.
    - Miscellaneous promotional material., ca.1965. (Box 54, Folder 4)
      Small format posters and promotional items, including one 7" vinyl LP and D.F. Jones' novel.
    - Miscellaneous., ca. 1968. (Box 54, Folder 5)
      Interviews and bios of Chase, data and credits about production and release, contracts, synopsis, and pitch for sequel.
    - Wardrobe., ca. 1968. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Shooting schedule., 1968. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Cast and crew., 1968. (Box 55, Folder 1)
      Contract memos, cast lists, and call sheets.
    - Contracts and agreements., 1965-1967. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Production budget., 1968. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Casting., 1968. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Production file., 1968. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Daily production reports., 1968-1969. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Budget., 1968-1969. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - American publicity posters., ca. 1970. (Box 67)
    - Production design drawing by G. Meyer. Man at computer., ca. 1968. (Box 76, Folder 1)
      Acrylic on paper; measures approx. 12" x 28." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawing by G. Meyer. Colossus complex corridor., ca. 1968. (Box 76, Folder 2)
      Acrylic on paper; measures approx. 10" x 26." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawing by G. Meyer. Desert camp tent interior., ca. 1968. (Box 76, Folder 3)
      Acrylic on paper; measures approx. 13" x 27." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawing by G. Meyer. Desert camp at sunset., ca. 1967. (Box 76, Folder 4)
      Acrylic on board; measures approx. 12" x 25." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawing. Desert camp and jeep., ca. 1967. (Box 76, Folder 5)
      Acrylic on board; measures approx. 20" x 30." Unsigned.
    - Production design drawings by G. Meyer. City scenes., ca. 1968. (Box 76, Folder 6)
      Acrylic on board; measures approx. 10" x 28." Signed by the artist. One 12" x 17" section of an oversize illustration of a similar scene, featuring a futuristic railway. The second section of this unsigned design is in box 93.
    - Production design drawing by Gene Johnson. Colossus complex exit bridge (side view)., ca. 1968. (Box 76, Folder 7)
      Acrylic on board; measures approx. 15" x 27." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawing by Gene Johnson. Colossus complex exit bridge (lower view)., ca. 1968. (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Preliminary production design sketches or storyboard. Colossus complex corridor., ca. 1968. (Box 76, Folder 9)
      Four copied charcoal renderings, mounted on board; each image measures approx. 6: x 13." Unsigned.
    - Preliminary production design sketches. Colossus monitor and printer interface (2 items)., ca. 1968. (Box 76, Folder 10)
      Three renderings in ink and acrylic on board; each sketch measures approx. 8" x 7." Unsigned.
    - Preliminary production design sketches. Video phones., ca. 1968. (Box 76, Folder 11)
      Three renderings in acrylic on board; each sketch measures approx. 8" x 12." Unsigned.
    - French and German publicity posters., ca. 1970. (Box 77)
    - Production design drawing. Colossus mountain complex (cut-away view)., ca. 1968. (Box 78)
      Acrylic on paper; measures approx. 24" x 31." Unsigned.
    - Production design drawing. Colossus complex corridor., ca. 1968. (Box 79)
      Acrylic on paper; measures approx. 24" x 38." Unsigned.
    - Production design drawing. Radiation belt gate with view of Colossus complex entrance., ca. 1968. (Box 81)
      Acrylic on board; measures approx. 20" x 33." Unsigned.
    - Production design drawings. Figures in red corridor., ca. 1968. (Box 82)
      Acrylic on paper and board; measures approx. 19" x 36" and 10 x 40." Unsigned.
    - Production design drawing by G. Meyer. Colossus complex corridor., ca. 1968. (Box 83)
      Acrylic and composite on paper, mounted and matted; measures approx. 14" x 36." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawing by G. Meyer. Colossus complex exit bridge (bird's-eye view)., ca. 1968. (Box 84)
      Acrylic on paper; measures approx. 15" x 34." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawing. C.P.O. watch room interior., ca. 1968. (Box 85)
      Acrylic on paper; measures approx. 19" x 36." Unsigned.
    - Production design drawing. Conference/map center., ca. 1968. (Box 86)
      Acrylic on board; measures approx. 15" x 34." Unsigned.
    - Production design sample. Circuit board., ca. 1968. (Box 87, Folder 2)
      Composite, matted. Measures approx. 10" x 16." Matted.
    - Lobby cards., no date. (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Art direction blueprints., 1968. (Box 88)
      Set construction plans for the Forbin quarters and conference room.
    - Production design drawing by G. Meyer. Missile silo interior., ca. 1968. (Box 89, Folder 1)
      Acrylic on paper; measures approx. 10" x 20." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawing by Gene Johnson. Radiation belt gate., ca. 1968.; [2 folders]. (Box 89, Folder 2-3)
      Acrylic on board; measures approx. 8" x 19." Signed by the artist.
    - Production design drawings. Colossus View Hotel and mountain vista., ca. 1968. (Box 89, Folder 4)
      Acrylic on board and plastic (multiple layers for changing view); measures approx. 15" x 20" and 12" x 24." Unsigned.
    - Original Colossus logo design., ca. 1968. (Box 89, Folder 5)
      Composite, matted. Measures approx. 9" x 12." Unsigned.
    - Production design drawings by G. Meyer. Conference center interior., ca. 1968. (Box 89, Folder 6)
      Acrylic on paper; each illustration measures approx. 10" x 24." Signed by the artist.
    - Preliminary production design sketches. Camera and transmitters., ca. 1968. (Box 89, Folder 7)
      Acrylic on board; measures approx. 30" x 24." Unsigned.
    - Production design drawing by Gene Johnson. Crowd gathering at Colossus complex entrance., ca. 1968. (Box 98)
      Acrylic on board and plastic (multiple layers for changing view); measures approx. 15" x 14." Signed by the artist.
  - Subseries 2C: High Ballin', 1976-1986.; 3 boxes.
    This subseries consists of production files and business files, photographs, and publicity materials. High Ballin' was widely released in the United States May 26, 1978 under Stanley Chase Productions. The film starred Peter Fonda, Jerry Reed, and Helen Shaver, and was directed by Peter Carter. The screenplay was written by Paul Edwards, Richard Robinson, and Stephen Schneck.
    - Contracts, correspondence, and agreements., 1976-1980. (Box 56, Folder 1-5)
    - Contracts, agreements and financial records., 1977-1986. (Box 57, Folder 1-6)
    - Publicity., 1978. (Box 57, Folder 7)
      Press kits, clippings, and assorted publicity materials.
    - Photographs., 1978. (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
    - Legal and financial documents., 1977-1982. (Box 58, Folder 3-4)
    - Production binder., 1980. (Box 58, Folder 5)
      Contents of a binder with production memos, cast and crew lists, schedules, call sheets, production reports, and a script.
  - Subseries 2D: Mack the Knife, 1955-1990.; 8 boxes.
    This subseries consists of production files and business files, legal documents, photographs, publicity materials, press clippings, and scripts. Mack the Knife was a theatrical motion picture adaptation of Kurt Weill and Bert Brecht's musical The Threepenny Opera, and was widely released in the United States February 2, 1990 under Stanley Chase Productions. The film starred Raul Julia, and was directed by Menahem Golan. Screenplay by Menahem Golan. For audio recordings of the cast production, see Series 4. Audio and visual materials.
    - Contracts, correspondence, and agreements pertaining to film rights for The Threepenny Opera., 1966-1989. (Box 99, Box 100, Box 101, Box 102)
    - Contracts, correspondence, and agreements pertaining to film rights for The Threepenny Opera., 1980-1989. (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Press kits., 1991. (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Chase v. Sossi., 1989-1992. (Box 103, Folder 3)
      Correspondence, legal documents and other records pertaining to the Chase v. Sossi case.
    - Financial records and agreements., 1955-1990. (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and pitches., 1980-1981. (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Publicity and reviews., 1978-1990. (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous., 1966-1990. (Box 104, Folder 2-4)
      Clippings, reviews, treatments, correspondence and other miscellaneous papers related to Mack the Knife and The Threepenny Opera.
    - Press and publicity., 1960-1990. (Box 105, Folder 1-3)
      Clippings, advertisements, and reviews.
    - Contracts, correspondence, and documents., 1987-1991. (Box 105, Folder 4)
      Pertaining to legalities of Mack the Knife.
    - Budgets., 1973, 1980. (Box 105, Folder 5)
      Picture budget details, and some budgets pertaining to a ca. 1973 production of The Threepenny Opera.
    - Screenplay--The Threepenny Opera adaptation by Robert David MacDonald., 1985, 1989. (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Screenplay--The Threepenny Opera adaptation by Marc Blitzstein., 1987 June 6. (Box 105, Folder 7)
      Screenplay by Joseph Goldman.
    - Screenplay--Adaptation by Alan Howard., 1980.; [3 folders]. (Box 106, Folder 1-3)
      First folder contains a tentative draft with a letter from Howard. The other two folders contain Alan Howard's screenplay, adapted from the screenplay by Ron Sossi and Chase.
    - Screenplay--Early draft., 1981 September 12. (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Screenplay--Adaptation by Sossi and Chase., ca. 1981.; [2 folders]. (Box 106, Folder 5-6)
      Heavily annotated.
    - Sossi film treatment of The Threepenny Opera., ca. 1981. (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Script--Final., 1987 September 9. (Box 106, Folder 8)
      Twelfth script, edited with significant annotations.
  - Subseries 2E: Miscellaneous productions, ca. 1973-1981.; 1 box, .25 oversize box, 1 map folder.
    This subseries consists of production files and business files, legal documents, photographs, publicity materials, original production design drawings, and posters. Major productions include: Welcome to Blood City (Stanley Chase Productions, 1977) and Fish Hawk (Stanley Chase Productions, 1979). Other items include posters from the films Flash Gordon, American Graffiti, and Blazing Saddles (signed by Mel Brooks).
    - Welcome to Blood City--Photographs., 1977. (Box 107, Folder 1-2)
    - Fish Hawk--Contracts, agreements and financial Records., 1978-1979. (Box 107, Folder 3-4)
      Includes production cost reports.
    - Fish Hawk--Publicity., 1980-1981. (Box 107, Folder 5-6)
      Clippings, advertisements, reviews, press kits, and photographs. See box 90 for Fish Hawk posters.
    - Kyle., 1994. (Box 107, Folder 7)
      Contracts and agreements.
    - Unidentified preliminary production design drawings by G. Meyer. Nude man and woman., no date. (Box 89, Folder 8)
      Preliminary storyboard illustrations, presumably for a film project, of a couple undressing. Acrylic on board; each illustration measures 3" x 8." Signed by the artist.
    - Miscellaneous posters., ca. 1973-1974. (Box 91)
      Posters for Flash Gordon, American Graffiti, and Blazing Saddles (signed by Mel Brooks).
  - Subseries 2F: Scripts, 1956-2001.; 19 Boxes.
    This subseries consists of assorted scripts and screenplays. Highlights include those produced or written by Chase, and scripts which later turned into successful productions.
    - Matheson, Richard. The Gunfighter (His Rise and Fall)., no date. (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Hunter, Evan. Spring on the Right Bank., no date. (Box 108, Folder 2)
      Screen treatment.
    - Bradbury, Ray. And the Rock Cried Out., no date. (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Wohl, Burton. Rio Lobo., 1968 May. (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Poe, James. The Gambler., no date. (Box 108, Folder 5)
      Marvin Birdt Associates, Ltd.
    - Matheson, Richard. Hell House., no date. (Box 108, Folder 6)